Carolina Cobo

<u>LinkedIn</u> | <u>Github</u> | <u>Portfolio</u>

Bloomfield Avenue, Dublin 4 ccobo.dev@gmail.com Nationality: European +353830695480

PERSONAL PROFILE

Over one year learning and building Full-Stack web applications, currently studying the Diploma in Full Stack Software Development in the Code Institute. I'm a technical Sourcer at MongoDB who is actively looking to move to the other side and condtribute to a team by building new products. I bring an excellent technical talent acquisition background that proves that I'm logical, responsive, ambitious, and resourceful.

EDUCATION

2020 - Currently: the Code Institute · Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp

2020 - Currently: Udemy Front End Development.

2021 - Currently: CS50 - Harvard (edX)

TECHNICAL SKILL SET

Technologies

- JavaScript
- HTML5/CSS3
- Python
- PHP

Databases

- MongoDB
- MySQL

Frameworks/Libraries

- Bootstrap
- jQuery
- WordPress
- Materialize
- Flask

Version Control UX Tools

- Git
- Github
- Balsamiq
- Figma

Click below to see some examples of my work







HTML and CSS

In this page you would find different popular Spanish recipes. Completed in HTML, CSS and Bootstrap, First Milestone Project in Code Institute course.



HTML, CSS and Bootstrap

Landing page for TinDog, an app to meet other other dogs nearby. Udemy course projec



OTHER INFORMATION

- Currently taking the Harvard CS50 course, this course covers computer science fundamentals using C, Python, HTML, CSS & JS.
- Currently reading Grokking Algorithms by Aditya Y. Bhargava and You Don't Know JS yet by Kyle Simpson.
- I participated in the St. Patrick's day Code Institute Hackathon.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Codu | Trainee Software Developer [Part-time]

Mar 2021 - Currently | Dublin, Ireland

IT outsourcing company that specialises in software development and consulting services. I've been collaborating part time with some projects at Codu while I'm completing my Degree at the Code Institute. Currently working on a project for an Insurance Company based in Spain.

MongoDB | Technical Sourcer [Full-time]

Jun 2020 - Currently | Dublin, Ireland

The leading modern, general-purpose database platform designed to unleash the power of software and data for developers and the applications they build. Primary duties in my current position are:

- Main programming languages I recruit for C/C++, Java and JavaScript.
- Find, engage, and activate high-quality passive candidates through Boolean, LinkedIn, and alternative search techniques, such as Stack Overflow, Github, HackerNews or Slack.
- Tools: Greenhouse, GEM, Calendly, Google Suite, Slack and Zoom.
- Strong knowledge and experience using CRM and ATS software Bullhorn, Linkedin recruiter.

Morgan McKinley | Technology Associate Recruitment Consultant & Technology Consultant

Jul 2019 - Jun 2020: Technology Recruitment Consultant | Dublin, Ireland

Jan 2019 - Jul 2019: Technology Associate Consultant | Dublin, Ireland

Morgan McKinley is a global professional services recruitment consultancy working in over ten verticals and offices in the U.K, Australia, China, Canada, France, Singapore, Ireland and Japan.

Jul 2019 - Jun 2020: Technology Recruitment Consultant

- Sourcing candidates through advertising, search and networking in the Python, DevOps, SRE & C++ market.
- Finding creative alternatives ways to finding passive candidates sourcing on LinkedIn & Bullhorn.
- Interviewing, selection and assessment for interviews of candidates.

Galgus | HR Trainee, HR Coordinator & HR Office Manager

Jan 2016 - Jun 2018 | Seville, Spain

Galgus is a telecommunications company that develops and markets a Wi-Fi technology currently being used by numerous OEMs and system integrators worldwide to deliver high-performing Wi-Fi networks.

Mar 2017 - Jul 2018: Human Resources Office Manager Jul 2016 - Mar 2017: Human Resources Coordinator

Jan 2016 - Jul 2016: HR Trainee

Axesor, Conocer Para decidir | Online Administration Intern

October 2014 - July 2015 | Granada, Spain

OTHER EDUCATION

2019 - 2020: CIPD Level 5 · Avado (Ireland)

2015 - 2017: Master in Management and Development of HR · University of Seville (Spain)

2010 - 2014: Labour Relations and HR degree · University of Granada (Spain)